(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Attention ご来場の皆様へ
Attention: To all visitors
公演中に声を出しての応援はご遠慮ください
ライト・拍手で応援をお願いします
Please refrain from vocal cheering during the performance.
Please support with lights and applause.
公演中は自席の前で立ってご観覧いただけます
You may stand in front of your seat during the show.
公演中は席の移動をお控えください
Please refrain from moving from your seat during the show.
マスクの着用にご協力ください
Please cooperate by wearing a mask.
COCOAを使用していだくため携帯電話の電源はオフにせず
マナーモードに設定してください
To allow for COCOA app usage, please do not turn off
your phone; instead, set it to silent mode.
撮影/録音/録画は禁止とさせていただきます
Photography, audio recording, and filming are prohibited.
#つながるホロライブDAY2
#ConnectingHololiveDAY2
hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish
キミとつくる 新しいストーリー
A new story we create together
ここから始まるよ
Starts right here
夢を追いかけて
Chasing our dreams
どこまでもいける
We can go anywhere
マスクの着用にご協力ください
Please cooperate by wearing a mask
携帯電話の電源はオフにせず マナーモードに設定してください
Please do not turn off your mobile phone, but set it to silent mode
撮影/録音/録画は禁止とさせていただきます
Photography, audio, and video recording are prohibited
公演中に声を出しての応援はご遠慮ください
Please refrain from vocal cheering during the performance
ライト・拍手で応援をお願いします
Please support with lights and clapping
公演中は自席の前で立ってご鑑賞いただけます
You may stand in front of your own seat to watch during the performance
Shiny Smily Story
響き合ってゆく
Resonating together
キミの笑顔が
Your smile is
最高のご褒美
The best reward
ずっと ずっと 追いかけていたい
I want to keep chasing it forever
もっと遠くまで
Even further
Shiny Smily Story
奏で合ってゆく
Playing music together
キミの想いが
Your feelings are
最高のご褒美
The best reward
ずっと ずっと 繋がっていたい
I want to stay connected forever
もっとその先へ
Even further beyond
Shiny Smily Story
夢の向こうへ
To the other side of our dreams
キミの隣が
Being by your side
最高のご褒美
Is the best reward
ずっと ずっと 笑っていたい
I want to keep smiling forever
もっと眩しく
Even more radiantly
本日、ホロライブ サードフェス リンク ユア ウィッシュ、
Today, for hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish,
ご来場いただきまして、誠にありがとうございます。
thank you very much for coming.
本公演におきまして、ご来場の皆様にお願いがございます。
For this performance, we have a request for all visitors.
新型コロナウイルス感染症拡大防止対策として、マスクの着用、手指の消毒、
As a measure to prevent the spread of COVID-19, please wear a mask and disinfect your hands,
ソーシャルディスタンスへのご協力をお願いしております。
and we ask for your cooperation with social distancing.
館内におきましても、周囲のお客様との密接を避け、
Also inside the building, please avoid close contact with surrounding customers,
大声での会話はお控えくださいますよう、お願いいたします。
and please refrain from loud conversations.
本公演は、全席指定となっております。
This performance has all reserved seating.
必ずご自身のお席にてご観覧いただきますよう、お願いいたします。
Please be sure to watch from your own seat.
本公演におきまして、携帯電話、スマートフォンの使用は禁止です。
The use of mobile phones and smartphones is prohibited during the performance.
スマートフォンは、新型コロナウイルス接触確認アプリ、COCOAを使用いただくため、
In order to use the COCOA COVID-19 contact confirmation app on your smartphone,
携帯電話の電源はオフにせず、マナーモードに設定してください。
please do not turn off your phone and set it to silent mode instead.
また、携帯電話、スマートフォンなどによる撮影、録音、録画は禁止とさせていただきます。
Also, filming, recording, or video recording with mobile phones or smartphones is prohibited.
万が一、撮影が発覚した場合は、データの削除の上、退場していただく場合もございます。
In the event that filming is discovered, data will be deleted and you may be asked to leave.
本公演におきまして、マスクの着用、手指の消毒、検温にご協力をお願いしております。
For this performance, we ask for your cooperation with masks, hand disinfection, and temperature checks.
スマートフォンは、COCOAを使用いただくため、
In order to use COCOA on your smartphone,
携帯電話の電源はオフにせず、マナーモードに設定してください。
please do not turn off your phone and set it to silent mode.
撮影、録音、録画は禁止とさせていただきます。
Filming, recording, and video recording are strictly prohibited.
係員の指示に従っていただけない場合は、ご退場していただく可能性がございます。
If you do not follow the staff's instructions, you may be asked to leave.
また、公演中には、お席の前で立ってご観覧いただくことが可能です。
Also, during the performance, you are allowed to stand and watch in front of your seat.
本公演は、客席の移動は禁止となっております。
In this performance, moving between seats is prohibited.
万が一、体調が悪くなりました場合は、すぐにお近くのスタッフへお申し出くださいますよう、お願いいたします。
In the event that you feel unwell, please inform a nearby staff member immediately.
公演終了後は、規制退場となります。
After the performance ends, there will be a regulated exit.
ブロックごとにアナウンスさせていただきますので、ご協力をお願いいたします。
We will announce the exit by block, so we ask for your cooperation.
スタッフの指示があるまで、ご自身のお席でお待ちください。
Please wait in your seat until you receive instructions from the staff.
最後に、本公演、会場内において、撮影用のカメラが入っております。
Finally, please note that there are recording cameras inside the venue for this performance.
お客様が映り込む可能性がございます。予め、ご了承をお願いいたします。
There is a possibility that audience members may be captured on film. We ask for your understanding.
それでは、開演まで今しばらくお待ちください。
Now, please wait a little longer until the performance begins.
本日、ホロライブ サードフェス リンク ユア ウィッシュ、
Today, for hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish,
ご来場いただきまして、誠にありがとうございます。
thank you very much for coming.
本公演におきまして、ご来場の皆様にお願いがございます。
For this performance, we have a request for all visitors.
新型コロナウイルス感染症拡大防止対策として、マスクの着用、手指の消毒、
As a measure to prevent the spread of COVID-19, please wear a mask and disinfect your hands,
ソーシャルディスタンスへのご協力をお願いしております。
and we ask for your cooperation with social distancing.
館内におきましても、周囲のお客様との密接を避け、
Also inside the building, please avoid close contact with surrounding customers,
大声での会話はお控えくださいますよう、お願いいたします。
and please refrain from loud conversations.
本公演は、全席指定となっております。
This performance has all reserved seating.
必ずご自身のお席にてご観覧いただきますよう、お願いいたします。
Please be sure to watch from your own seat.
本公演におきまして、携帯電話、スマートフォンの使用は禁止です。
The use of mobile phones and smartphones is prohibited during the performance.
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 公式ペンライトカラーまとめ
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 Official Penlight Colors
公式アイテム：ウインドブレーカー / トートバッグ / サコッシュ
Official Items: Windbreaker / Tote Bag / Sacoche
公式アイテム：ロゴクッション / ラバーバンド / タペストリー
Official Items: Logo Cushion / Rubber Band / Tapestry
限定アイテム：コラボキャップ / サラサクリップ 5色セット
Limited Items: Collaboration Cap / Sarasa Clip 5-set
公式アイテム：ランダム缶バッジ (ホロライブ / ホロスターズ)
Official Items: Random Badges (hololive / HOLOSTARS)
公式アイテム：アクリルキーホルダー
Official Items: Acrylic Keyholders
公式アイテム：クリアファイルセット / アクリルジオラマ
Official Items: Clear File Set / Acrylic Diorama
公式アイテム：トランプ 2022 / パンフレット
Official Items: Playing Cards 2022 / Pamphlet
限定アイテム：ロゴコーチジャケット / カレッジロゴスウェット
Limited Items: Logo Coach Jacket / College Logo Sweat
限定アイテム：ロゴ Tシャツ / SSS ロングTシャツ
Limited Items: Logo T-shirts / SSS L/S T-shirts
Attention: マスク着用 / COCOA利用 / 撮影・録音禁止
Attention: Wear Mask / Use COCOA / No Filming
Attention: 声出し禁止 / 席での観賞 / ライト・拍手で応援
Attention: No Cheering / Stay at Seat / Light & Clapping
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ：プレミアムブースター
Weiss Schwarz: Premium Booster
アクリルカードスタンド / カードバインダー
Acrylic Card Stand / Card Binder
公式アイテム：トレーディングピンバッジ
Official Items: Trading Pins
プレートアクリルスタンド / B2タペストリー
Plate Acrylic Stand / B2 Tapestry
公式アイテム：耐水シール
Official Items: Waterproof Stickers
缶＆ハンドタオル
Can & Hand Towel
Attention: マスク着用 / COCOA利用 / 撮影・録音禁止
Attention: Wear Mask / Use COCOA / No Filming
ご来場の皆様へ：マスクの着用、COCOAの使用、撮影・録音の禁止にご協力ください。
To all visitors: Please cooperate with wearing masks, using COCOA, and refraining from filming or recording.
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ
Weiß Schwarz
ホロライブプロダクションのブースターパックでも、
Even with the Hololive Production booster pack,
止まらないヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiß Schwarz never stops!
ブースターパック ホロライブプロダクション 好評発売中！
Booster Pack Hololive Production, now on sale!
ブシロード
Bushiroad
アニメが大好きな中外鉱業コンテンツ部です！
We are the Chugai Mining Contents Department, and we love anime!
もっともっと！
More and more!
アニメを楽しみたい、そんな想いでアニメグッズを企画開発して
With the desire to enjoy anime, we plan and develop anime goods...
インターネットで販売しています！
...and sell them on the internet!
アニメとコラボしたカフェもやってます。
We also run cafes that collaborate with anime.
最新情報はTwitterで！
Check Twitter for the latest information!
hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish
OFFICIAL ITEMS: ペンライト、Tシャツ、マフラータオル
OFFICIAL ITEMS: Penlight, T-shirt, Muffler Towel
OFFICIAL ITEMS: ウィンドブレーカー、トートバッグ、サコッシュ
OFFICIAL ITEMS: Windbreaker, Tote Bag, Sacoche
SPECIAL LIMITED ITEMS: hololive × MANGART BEAMS
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 OFFICIAL ITEMS
Attention ご来場の皆様へ
マスク着用、マナーモード設定、撮影録音禁止
Attention to all visitors:
Please wear a mask, set to silent mode, and no recording.
声出し応援禁止、自席での観覧、席移動禁止
No shouting, please stay at your assigned seat, and no moving between seats.
#つながるホロライブDAY2
hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish
#ConnectingHololiveDAY2
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 OFFICIAL ITEMS
Attention ご来場の皆様へ
マスク着用、マナーモード設定、撮影録音禁止
Attention to all visitors:
Please wear a mask, set to silent mode, and no recording.
Attention ご来場の皆様へ / マスクの着用にご協力ください
Attention to all attendees: Please cooperate by wearing a mask.
携帯電話はマナーモードに設定してください / 撮影・録音・録画は禁止です
Please set your phone to silent mode. Photography and recording are prohibited.
声を出しての応援はご遠慮ください / 自席の前で立ってご観覧いただけます
Please refrain from vocal cheering. You may stand at your seat to watch.
席の移動はお控えください / ライト・拍手で応援をお願いします
Please refrain from moving seats. Cheer with light sticks and applause.
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ プレミアムブースター / ホロライブプロダクション
Weiss Schwarz Premium Booster: hololive production
ブシロード アクリルカードスタンド / カードバインダー
Bushiroad Acrylic Card Stand / Card Binder
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 OFFICIAL ITEMS / トレーディング缶バッジ
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 OFFICIAL ITEMS / Trading Tin Badges
プレートアクリルスタンド / B2タペストリー
Plate Acrylic Stand / B2 Tapestry
耐水シール
Waterproof Stickers
缶＆ハンドタオル
Tin Case & Hand Towel
Attention ご来場の皆様へ / マスク着用にご協力ください / 撮影・録音・録画は禁止です
Attention to attendees: Please wear a mask. Photography and recording are prohibited.
声出し応援禁止 / 自席での立ち見可 / 席移動禁止 / ライト・拍手で応援をお願いします
No vocal cheering. Standing at seat OK. No moving seats. Cheer with lights and applause.
hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish DAY 2 / #つながるホロライブDAY2
hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish DAY 2 / #ConnectHololiveDay2
ペンライト / Tシャツ / マフラータオル
Penlight / T-shirt / Muffler Towel
公式ペンライトカラーまとめ
Official Penlight Colors List
ウインドブレーカー / トートバッグ / サコッシュ
Windbreaker / Tote Bag / Sacoche
ロゴクッション / ラバーバンド / タペストリー
Logo Cushion / Rubber Band / Tapestry
コラボキャップ / サラサクリップ5本セット
Collaboration Cap / Sarasa Clip (Set of 5)
ランダム缶バッジ
Random Tin Badges
アクリルキーホルダー
Acrylic Keychains
クリアファイルセット / アクリルジオラマ
Clear File Set / Acrylic Diorama
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 OFFICIAL ITEMS
クリアファイルセット / アクリルジオラマ
Clear File Set / Acrylic Diorama
トランプ 2022 / パンフレット
Playing Cards 2022 / Pamphlet
SPECIAL LIMITED ITEMS - MANGART BEAMS
ロゴ コーチジャケット / カレッジロゴ クルースウェット
Logo Coach Jacket / College Logo Crew Sweat
ロゴ S/S Tシャツ / SSS L/S Tシャツ
Logo S/S T-shirt / SSS L/S T-shirt
Attention - ご来場の皆様へ
Attention - To all attendees
マスクの着用にご協力ください / マナーモードに設定してください / 撮影・録音・録画は禁止
Please cooperate by wearing a mask / Please set to silent mode / Photography and recording are prohibited
公演中に声を出しての応援はご遠慮ください / 自席の前で立ってご鑑賞いただけます / 席の移動はお控えください
Please refrain from cheering out loud during the performance / You may stand in front of your seat / Please refrain from moving between seats
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ プレミアムブースター ホロライブプロダクション
Weiβ Schwarz Premium Booster hololive Production
ブシロード アクリルカードスタンド / カードバインダー
Bushiroad Acrylic Card Stand / Card Binder
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 トレーディングカード vol.1 - vol.7
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 Trading Card vol.1 - vol.7
プレートアクリルスタンド / B2タペストリー
Plate Acrylic Stand / B2 Tapestry
耐水シール
Waterproof Stickers
缶&ハンドタオル
Can & Hand Towel
[Repeat] Attention - ご来場の皆様へ
[Repeat] Attention - To all attendees
#つながるホロライブDAY2 - hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish
#Connect hololive DAY 2 - hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish
ペンライト / Tシャツ / マフラータオル
Penlight / T-shirt / Muffler Towel
PENLIGHT COLORS - 公式ペンライトカラーまとめ
PENLIGHT COLORS - Official Penlight Color Summary
ウィンドブレーカー / トートバッグ / サコッシュ
Windbreaker / Tote Bag / Sacoche
ロゴクッション / ラバーバンド / タペストリー
Logo Cushion / Rubber Band / Tapestry
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 OFFICIAL ITEMS
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 SPECIAL LIMITED ITEMS
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiss Schwarz!
ホロライブプロダクションの
With the hololive production
ブースターパックでも、止まらないヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
booster pack, Weiss Schwarz is unstoppable!
ブースターパック ホロライブプロダクション、好評発売中！
Booster Pack hololive production, now on sale!
ブシロード！
Bushiroad!
アニメが大好きな中外鉱業コンテンツ部です！
We are the Chugai Mining Content Department, and we love anime!
アニメを楽しみたい！
We want to enjoy anime!
そんな想いでアニメグッズを企画開発してインターネットで販売しています！
With that in mind, we plan, develop, and sell anime goods online!
アニメとコラボしたカフェもやってます。
We also run cafes in collaboration with anime.
最新情報はTwitterで！
Check Twitter for the latest information!
Attention ご来場の皆様へ
Attention to all visitors
マスクの着用にご協力ください
Please cooperate by wearing a mask
携帯電話の電源はオフにせず マナーモードに設定してください
Do not turn off your mobile phone; please set it to silent mode
撮影/録音/録画は禁止とさせていただきます
Photography, recording, and filming are prohibited
ライト・拍手で応援をお願いします
Please show your support with lights and applause
#つながるホロライブDAY2
#LinkYourWishDAY2
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment until the performance begins
hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish ペンライト
hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish Penlight
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 OFFICIAL ITEMS
通販でも販売中！
Now available via mail order!
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022
公式ペンライトカラーまとめ
Official Penlight Colors List
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 SPECIAL LIMITED ITEMS
hololive EN × NEW ERA COLLABORATION CAP
hololive × MANGART BEAMS
Attention ご来場の皆様へ
マスクの着用にご協力ください
Attention: To all attendees
Please cooperate by wearing a mask.
携帯電話はマナーモードに設定してください
撮影/録音/録画は禁止とさせていただきます
Set phones to silent mode.
Photography, recording, and filming are prohibited.
公演中に声を出しての応援はご遠慮ください
ライト・拍手で応援をお願いします
Please refrain from cheering out loud.
Please cheer using lights and clapping.
公演中は自席の前で立ってご鑑賞いただけます
公演中は席の移動をお控えください
You may stand at your seat to watch.
Please refrain from moving between seats.
hololive SUPER EXPO 2022 OFFICIAL ITEMS
プレミアムブースター ホロライブプロダクション
Premium Booster: Hololive Production
ホロライブ６期生の沙花叉クロヱです！
I'm Sakamata Chloe of hololive 6th Gen!
本日は「hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish Supported By ヴァイスシュヴァルツ Day 2」にご来場いただき、ありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming to "hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish Supported By Weiss Schwarz Day 2" today!
同じくホロライブ６期生の風真いろはでござる。
I am Kazama Iroha, also of hololive 6th Gen.
今日は私たちが場内アナウンスを担当いたします。今日一日、よろしくお願いいたします。
We will be in charge of the venue announcements today. We look forward to spending the day with you.
開演の前にお客様にご案内がございます。まずは、会場のみなさまへのご案内です。
Before the show starts, we have some information for our guests. First, for those in the venue.
ロビー、客席内では、マスク着用が必須となります。
Wearing a mask is mandatory in the lobby and at your seats.
公演中の掛け声などは、新型コロナウイルス感染予防の観点からご遠慮ください。
Please refrain from shouting or cheering during the performance to prevent the spread of COVID-19.
ぜひ、拍手やペンライトなどでの応援をお願いします。
Please support us with clapping and penlights.
また、会場内では立って応援いただいても問題ございませんが、周りのお客様にご迷惑にならないようご配慮お願いいたします。
Also, while you may stand during the show, please be considerate of those around you.
続いて、配信をご覧のみなさまへのご案内です。
Next, some information for those watching the stream.
本ライブの録音、録画、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固くお断りいたします。
Recording, filming, mirror streaming, and illegal uploads of this live performance are strictly prohibited.
その代わり、スクリーンショットでの撮影をしていただくことや、SNSで感想を呟いていただくことは大歓迎なので...
Instead, taking screenshots and sharing your thoughts on social media is very welcome...
みなさん、ハッシュタグ「#つながるホロライブDAY2」で感想を呟いて、SNSもいっぱい盛り上げてください！
...so please use the hashtag #hololiveLinkYourWishDay2 and help liven up social media!
本ライブ配信はデータ通信量が多くなることが想定されるため、スマートフォンでご覧になる場合は、Wi-Fi環境でのご利用を推奨いたします。
As this live stream is expected to consume a lot of data, we recommend using a Wi-Fi environment if you are watching on a smartphone.
インターネット回線の接続が不安定な場合は、配信動画のクオリティを保証できませんので、ご了承ください。
Please understand that we cannot guarantee the quality of the stream if your internet connection is unstable.
また、最善の準備を行いライブ配信を実施いたしますが、生配信である特性上、不慮の障害で一時停止や映像の乱れなどが起こる可能性があることを、あらかじめご了承ください。
Also, while we are doing our best to prepare for the stream, please understand that due to the nature of live broadcasting, unexpected issues may cause pauses or video distortions.
それでは、開演までもうしばらくお待ちください。
Well then, please wait a little longer until the show starts.
Hello everyone! I am Kronii from hololive English -Council-.
I am Baelz from hololive English -Council-. Thank you everyone for coming to hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish Supported By Weiss Schwarz Day 2!
And I'm Fauna, also from hololive English -Council-. Today we will be in charge of all the announcements within the venue. We hope you have an amazing time!
Before the show starts, we have some quick announcements. We would like to first address the audience here today.
Masks are mandatory and must be worn in the lobby and auditorium. Please refrain from shouting during the performances in order to prevent the spread of coronavirus.
We would love it if you support us with handclapping and penlights.
In addition, it is fine to stand up and cheer within the venue. However, please be considerate of those around you when doing so.
Next is a short reminder to all of you who will be watching the livestream. It is strictly prohibited to record, tape, mirror, or illegally upload this live performance.
However, you are definitely welcome to take pictures and share your experiences on all social media platforms. If you decide to do so, please use the hashtag #hololiveLinkYourWishDay2 and feel free to share your thoughts on social media.
This live performance is expected to require a large amount of data transmission and bandwidth. We heavily recommend that you use Wi-Fi when viewing this event on your smartphone.
If your internet connection is unstable, we cannot guarantee the quality of the delivered video. Although we will do our best to prepare for the live broadcast, please keep in mind that due to the nature of live broadcasts, there is a possibility of pauses or distortions in the video due to unforeseen problems.
Nama saya Reine dari hololive Indonesia Generasi 2.
My name is Reine from hololive Indonesia Generation 2.
Terima kasih telah datang ke hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish Supported By Weiss Schwarz Day 2 pada hari ini.
Thank you for coming to hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish Supported By Weiss Schwarz Day 2 today.
Dan aku Ollie dari hololive Indonesia Generasi 2.
And I'm Ollie from hololive Indonesia Generation 2.
Hari ini kami akan bertanggung jawab untuk membacakan pengumuman.
Today we will be responsible for reading the announcements.
Semoga hari ini akan menjadi hari yang menyenangkan.
We hope today will be a fun day.
Pertama-tama, ada beberapa pengumuman untuk para tamu.
First of all, there are some announcements for our guests.
Kepada para tamu,
To our guests,
kami mohon untuk selalu memakai masker saat berada di lobi maupun tempat duduk.
we ask that you always wear a mask while in the lobby or in your seats.
Kami mohon juga untuk tidak mengeluarkan suara
We also ask that you do not make any noise
pada saat konser untuk mencegah penyebaran virus Corona.
during the concert to prevent the spread of the Coronavirus.
Tolong dukung kami dengan tepukan tangan dan penlight.
Please support us with clapping and penlights.
Anda diperbolehkan untuk mendukung sambil berdiri.
You are allowed to support while standing.
Namun harap berhati-hati agar tidak merepotkan tamu lain.
However, please be careful not to inconvenience other guests.
Selanjutnya adalah pengumuman
Next is an announcement
untuk para pendatang yang menonton livestream.
for visitors watching the livestream.
Anda dilarang untuk merekam, menayangkan,
You are prohibited from recording, broadcasting,
atau mengupload ulang stream konser secara ilegal.
or re-uploading the concert stream illegally.
Tapi sebagai gantinya, anda dianjurkan untuk upload screenshot
But instead, you are encouraged to upload screenshots
dan posting mengenai konser kami di media sosial.
and post about our concert on social media.
Mari gunakan tagar #つながるホロライブDAY2
Let's use the hashtag #つながるホロライブDAY2
di media sosial saat posting sambutan mengenai acara ini ya.
on social media when posting your thoughts about this event.
Karena konser live ini akan menggunakan data berukuran besar,
Because this live concert will use a large amount of data,
kami menyarankan penggunaan Wi-Fi jika anda menonton dari smartphone.
we recommend using Wi-Fi if you are watching from a smartphone.
Jika kualitas koneksi internet anda tidak memadai,
If your internet connection quality is inadequate,
kami tidak bisa menjanjikan kualitas video. Kami mohon pengertiannya.
we cannot guarantee video quality. We ask for your understanding.
Kami berkomitmen untuk mempersiapkan livestream ini
We are committed to preparing this livestream
dengan sebaik mungkin.
as best as possible.
Namun karena ini merupakan acara yang tayang secara langsung,
However, since this is a live-broadcasted event,
tetap ada kemungkinan terjadinya masalah teknis. Kami mohon pengertiannya.
there is still a possibility of technical issues occurring. We ask for your understanding.
Kami mohon untuk menunggu sebentar sampai pertunjukannya dimulai.
Please wait a moment until the performance begins.
本日もホロライブ 3rd fes. Link Your Wish Supported by ヴァイスシュヴァルツ Day 2 にご来場いただきありがとうございますでござる。
Thank you all for coming to hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish Supported by Weiss Schwarz Day 2 today!
まもなく開演します！
We're about to start!
みんな、準備はいいでござるか？
Everyone, are you ready?
せーの！
Ready, set...
Day 2、スタート！
Day 2, start!
ときのそら / TOKINO SORA
TOKINO SORA
ロボ子さん / ROBOCOSAN
ROBOCOSAN
夜空メル / YOZORA MEL
YOZORA MEL
アキ・ローゼンタール / AKI ROSENTHAL
AKI ROSENTHAL
湊あくあ / MINATO AQUA
MINATO AQUA
紫咲シオン / MURASAKI SHION
MURASAKI SHION
百鬼あやめ / NAKIRI AYAME
NAKIRI AYAME
癒月ちょこ / YUZUKI CHOCO
YUZUKI CHOCO
大神ミオ / OOKAMI MIO
OOKAMI MIO
猫又おかゆ / NEKOMATA OKAYU
NEKOMATA OKAYU
兎田ぺこら / USADA PEKORA
USADA PEKORA
不知火フレア / SHIRANUI FLARE
SHIRANUI FLARE
角巻わため / TSUNOMAKI WATAME
TSUNOMAKI WATAME
雪花ラミィ / YUKIHANA LAMY
YUKIHANA LAMY
獅白ぼたん / SHISHIRO BOTAN
SHISHIRO BOTAN
森カリオペ / MORI CALLIOPE
MORI CALLIOPE
小鳥遊キアラ / TAKANASHI KIARA
TAKANASHI KIARA
アユンダ・リス / AYUNDA RISU
AYUNDA RISU
アイラニ・イオフィフティーン / AIRANI IOFIFTEEN
AIRANI IOFIFTEEN
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's let our fresh, racing hearts resound
最高の時間、最高の仲間と
With the best time and the best friends
ひらめきに乗って
Riding on inspiration
イエーイ！
Yay!
覚えてるかな？ 最初の歌
Do you remember? The very first song
少しだけで、私の声が震えていた
My voice was shaking just a little bit
あの日から続く未来は
The future that has continued from that day
みんなと掴んだ今日だよ
Is the "today" we've grasped together
もっともっともっともっと加速するハート
Our hearts are accelerating more and more
一緒に行こうよ どこまでも
Let's go together, wherever it may lead
Are you ready? 準備は OK?
Are you ready? Are you prepared?
開け 夢の扉を
Open the door to our dreams
1, 2, 3! 煌めきライター
1, 2, 3! Sparkling Writer
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's let our fresh, racing hearts resound
最高の時間、最高の仲間と
With the best time and the best friends
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
I'm here because you found me
君に会いたく...
I want to meet you...
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ
I came here because I wanted to see you
みんなで歌おう
Let's all sing together
終わらないメロディー
The unending melody
きらめきに乗って
Riding on the sparkle
届いてるかな　私の声 (My voice)
Is it reaching you? My voice (My voice)
届けたいのは　君に笑顔
What I want to deliver is a smile to you
理想と遠さに　悔しくて
I was frustrated by the distance from my ideals
みんなと泣き笑ったね
We cried and laughed together, didn't we?
ぎゅっとぎゅっとぎゅっとぎゅっと　全て抱きしめて
Tightly, tightly, tightly, tightly, embracing everything
一緒に行こう　どこまでも (Alright!) 準備はOK?
Let's go together, no matter how far (Alright!) Are you ready?
進め希望の道を　1・2・3
Advance on the path of hope, 1, 2, 3
きらめきライター
Sparkling Writer
好きな気持ち　カラフルに奏でたいんだ
I want to perform my feelings of love colorfully
最高の場所　最高のみんなと
In the best place, with the best people
ここにいるよ　幻なんかじゃない
I'm here, it's not a phantom
君の心が　幸せに染まるように
So that your heart may be dyed in happiness
重ねていくハーモニー　きらめき纏って
Harmonies that we layer, draped in sparkle
歌い続けたいな
I want to keep singing
踊り続けたいな
I want to keep dancing
そんな願い　わがままもいいでしょ？
Is it okay to have such a selfish wish?
だって楽しすぎて　もっと笑いたい
Because it's so much fun, I want to laugh more
輝くステージで　もっともっとお願い　ずっと (Oh yeah!)
On the shining stage, more and more, please, forever (Oh yeah!)
嬉しい楽しい　愛しいだけじゃ語れない
I can't express it just with happy, fun, and dear
今も今も　悩みはあるけれど
Even now, even now, I still have worries
ここにいるよ私　ここにいるよ
I am here, I am here
君と同じ世界を　見つめて (Ready!)
Looking at the same world as you (Ready!)
きらめきライター　生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Sparkling Writer, let the freshly born excitement resonate
最高の時間　最高の仲間と
In the best time, with the best comrades
ここにいるよ　見つけてくれたから
I'm here, because you found me
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ　みんなで歌おう
I came here because I wanted to see you, let's sing together
終わらないメロディー
The unending melody
きらめきに乗って
Riding on the sparkle
きらめき纏って (Yeah!)
Draped in sparkle (Yeah!)
アキ・ローゼンタール AKI ROSENTHAL
AKI ROSENTHAL
不知火フレア SHIRANUI FLARE
SHIRANUI FLARE
雪花ラミィ YUKIHANA LAMY
YUKIHANA LAMY
2日目も昨日に負けないくらい盛り上がっていくよ！
Day 2 will be just as exciting as yesterday!
幕張、みんなの声聞こえてるよ！
Makuhari, I can hear everyone's voices!
しっかりペンライト振って一緒に盛り上がろう！
Wave your penlights hard and let's get excited together!
思い通りにいかないことだらけ
Full of things that don't go as planned
どうしようもなくて自己嫌悪
Helpless and full of self-hatred
八百万の痛みや苦しみから　逃げ込める場所を探してる
Searching for a place to escape from countless pains and sufferings
生き急いだ路の隙間に引きこもって
Shutting myself away in the gaps of a path lived in haste
月も太陽も無視して眠ろう
Ignoring the moon and the sun, let's sleep
生まれてきたことの意味なんて　知らない　分かんないよ
The meaning of being born, I don't know, I don't understand
でもそんな
But such a...
...春に想える出来事
...something that feels like spring.
それは君がもっともっと素敵になれる
It's that you have the power
力があるって
to become more and more wonderful,
教えてるんだよ
that's what it's telling you.
そうさ神のまにまに
That's right, at God's mercy,
仰せのままに
just as he commands,
誰だって地球を愛してる
everyone loves the Earth.
飲めや歌えやどんちゃん騒ぎ
Drink and sing and make a big fuss,
たまにゃそんなのもいいね
sometimes that's okay too.
そうさ北も南も
That's right, north and south,
右も左も
right and left,
なんだかんだ地球を愛してる
somehow we all love the Earth.
泥んこだけど歩いて行ける
Covered in mud, but we can keep walking,
まだまだ先は長いさ
there's still a long way to go.
ただ正しい人でいたいだけ
I just want to be a righteous person,
きっと誰もがそう願っているけど
surely everyone wishes for that, but
八百万の心の醜さに
the ugliness of the myriad hearts
苦しまされる毎日
makes every day a struggle.
僕が生まれてきたこと
The fact that I was born,
奇跡と言えば聞こえはいいけど
it sounds nice to call it a miracle,
それはきっと偶然すぎなくて
but it's surely nothing more than a coincidence,
やっぱり意味なんてないさ
after all, there's no meaning to it.
でも例えば君にいじわるをする奴が
But for example, if someone is being mean to you,
いるなら
if they are,
それは君がとっても素敵な人だって
it's because you're such a wonderful person,
教えてるんだよ
that's what it's telling you.
教えてるんだよー
That's what it's telling you!
そうさ神のまにまに
That's right, at God's mercy,
仰せのままに
just as he commands,
誰だって地球を愛してる
everyone loves the Earth.
僕が笑って君も笑えば
If I laugh and you laugh too,
許せないことなんてないよ
there's nothing that can't be forgiven.
そうさ男も女も
That's right, men and women,
恋しかるべき
should fall in love,
そんな風に地球は回ってる
that's how the Earth turns.
泥んこだけど歩いて行こう
Covered in mud, but let's keep walking,
まだまだ先は長いさ
there's still a long way to go.
本当に大事なものなんて
What's truly important,
あんがいくだらないことの中にあるよ
is actually found within trivial things.
ときにはみんなで馬鹿騒ぎ
Sometimes everyone joins in a wild spree,
裸踊りで大笑い
laughing out loud with a naked dance!
そうさ神のまにまに
That's right, at God's mercy,
仰せのままに
just as he commands,
もっともっと自分を愛せるよ
you can love yourself more and more.
鏡を見てごらんよもう分かるでしょ
Look in the mirror, you'll see now,
みんなを照らす光さ
you're the light that shines on everyone.
そうさ神のまにまに
That's right, at God's mercy,
みんなありがとう
thank you everyone,
やっぱり地球を愛してる
after all, we love the Earth.
花も咲かそう大きな花を
Let's make flowers bloom, big flowers,
天まで届くくらいの
high enough to reach the heavens!
La la la...
はぁ... はぁ... うわぁ...
(Heavy breathing) Whoa...
hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish DAY2
Hololive 3rd Fes. Link Your Wish Day 2
いよいよ始まりましたー！
has finally begun!
イエーイ！
Yay!
皆さんこんにちはー！
Hello everyone!
こんにちはー！
Hello!
ホロライブ1期生、異世界からやってきた
Hololive 1st Generation, the half-elf from another world
ハーフエルフのアキ・ローゼンタールです。アローナ！
who came from another world, Aki Rosenthal. Aloha!
アキ・ローゼンタールです！
I'm Aki Rosenthal!
イエーイ！
Yay!
そしてー、ホロライブ3期生の不知火フレアです。アローナ！
And then, I'm Shiranui Flare from Hololive 3rd Gen. Aloha!
アローナ！
Aloha!
あれおかしいな。こんアロ... あれ次は？
Wait, that's weird. Kon-Alo... wait, what's next?
えー、顔が肝臓、ホロライブ5期生の
Uh, my face is the liver, Hololive 5th Gen's
雪花ラミィです。アローナ！
Yukihana Lamy. Aloha!
アローナ！あれ肝臓？
Aloha! Wait, liver?
色々なんか混ざっててよく分からないけれど、私たち3人合わせて...
A lot of things are mixed up and I'm not sure what's happening, but the three of us...
ホロライブのハーフエルフ組です！
are Hololive's Half-Elf group!
アローナじゃないんかい。
Wait, it's not Aloha?
ここは違うよ。
Not here.
ここは違うよ。ホロライブのね、ハーフエルフ...
Not here. Hololive's half-elf...
うん。はい。3人がね、初めて組むユニットで...
Yes. The three of us formed a unit for the first time...
そう。はい。
Yes. Right.
「神のまにまに」を踊らせていただきましたー！
and we performed "Kami no Mani Mani"!
イエーイ！どうだったー？
Yay! How was it?
さあこの3人でね、ずっとやりたかったのよ。
I've always wanted to do this with these three.
そうなんですよ。
That's right.
で、この曲はね、ラミィちゃんが提案してくれたんだよね。
And Lamy-chan suggested this song.
そうなんです。もう...
Yes, that's right. I...
このハーフエルフ組でこの曲を歌いたいと思ってたんです。
I've always wanted to sing this song with this half-elf group.
でも、叶って本当によかったです。楽しかった！
I'm so glad it came true. It was so much fun!
楽しかったけど、練習もすっごい難しかったよね。
It was fun, but practice was really difficult, wasn't it?
結構なんか、ステップがサビとか激しかったから、
The steps in the chorus were quite intense,
結構心配してたもんね。
so we were pretty worried.
そこはね、本当にアキ先輩、フレア先輩、ありがとうございました！
For that, Aki-senpai and Flare-senpai, thank you so much!
いいってことだよ、別に。後輩を助けるのはね...
Don't mention it. Helping our junior is...
...先輩として当然のことだから。
...only natural as seniors.
あのステップ、みんなやっちゃった。
We all ended up doing that step.
これちょっと、照れ隠しの時に...
Use this when you're trying to hide your embarrassment...
ぜひ使ってって、これ。ぜひ使っていきます。
Please use it. I'll definitely use it.
使っていきます。あげる、あげる。
I'll use it. Here you go, here you go.
ということで、ホロライブのね、サードフェスの2デイズ目、いよいよ始まりましたー！
And so, the 2nd day of hololive's 3rd fes has finally begun!
昨日も素晴らしいライブステージだったんですけども、
Yesterday's live stage was wonderful as well,
2デイズのみんなも頑張って練習してきたので、ぜひ見守っててください。
but everyone on day 2 has also practiced hard, so please watch over us.
はい、ではみんなはさ、緊張してる？
Right, so, is everyone nervous?
緊張します！こんな会場広いんですよ。
I'm nervous! The venue is so huge.
そうだよね、私もちょっとしたんだ。
You're right, I was a little bit too.
そうだよ。ちょっと緊張してた。もう始まってたよ、すでに。もうなんだったら歌ったのに。
That's right. I was a bit nervous. It had already started, after all. Even though we already sang.
なんてったって、歌ったのに、緊張してきた。
Even though I've already sung, I'm getting nervous.
あ、でもね、そう、ラミィちゃんのアイドル衣装が！
Oh, but, that's right, Lamy-chan's idol outfit!
そうなんです。ライブでは初めてのお披露目になります。
That's right. This is its first reveal at a live performance.
見せて見せて！くるくるー。かわいい！
Show us, show us! Spin around. So cute!
帽子もついてる。かわいいー。ありがとうございます。
It even has a hat. So cute. Thank you.
そうなんです、これ。雪の結晶も入ってて。もうここね、アイドルステージです。
Yes, this part here. It has snowflake patterns in it. This is the idol stage.
本当に、憧れのライブステージで、先輩と一緒にここに立てることが、本当に嬉しいです。
I'm truly happy to be able to stand here on this dream live stage with my seniors.
もっといろんな人に見せてあげたいね。端っこにも見せてあげに行こうよ。
We want to show it to even more people. Let's go show it to the people at the edges too.
2階席のみんなー！みんなー！3階席のみんなもー！
Everyone in the 2nd floor seats! Everyone in the 3rd floor seats too!
あっちだ、あっち！ゴー、ゴー！2階席のみんなー！
Over there, over there! Go, go! Everyone in the 2nd floor seats!
3階席のみんなー！戻ってきた、真ん中、真ん中。
Everyone in the 3rd floor seats! We're back to the center, the center.
それでは、お待たせしました。アロナ席のみんなー！
Now then, thanks for waiting. Everyone in the Alo-na seats!
待って待って、抜き駆けはダメだよ。エルフレのみんな、雪民のみんなー！
Wait, wait, no getting ahead! Everyone of the El-friends, everyone of the Yukimin!
アロナのみんなですよ！アロナのみんなー！ヤッホー！
It's everyone of the Alo-na! Everyone of the Alo-na! Yoo-hoo!
そしてそして、最後にコメントのみんなー！見えてるー！
And and, finally, everyone in the comments! We see you!
いや、楽しいですね、こうやってレスポンスがいただけて。すごく楽しいです。
Wow, it's so fun to get a response like this. It's so much fun.
でもね、そろそろお時間みたい。やだー！
But, it looks like it's almost time. No way!
まだここにいたい。まだいたいけど、
I still want to be here. I want to stay too, but...
そろそろ怒られそうなので。次の曲に行きましょうか。
...I think we're about to get scolded. Shall we move on to the next song?
ライブはまだまだ前半戦！皆さん、この後もぜひぜひ盛り上げてください。
The live is still only in the first half! Everyone, please keep the excitement going after this.
せーの、つながるホロライブ！
One, two, Connected hololive!
紫咲シオン
Murasaki Shion
百鬼あやめ
Nakiri Ayame
無礼法馬鹿見てないで
Don't look at me like a fool
ウラパパパパラリラ踊れよ
Ura-pa-pa-pa-pa-ra-ri-ra, dance
魔界学校の優等生
The honor student of the demon world school
華やかな我が儘を称えよ
Praise my colorful selfishness
ナイナイバでこっち向いて
Peek-a-boo, look this way
逆さまの未来を咲かせよ
Make an upside-down future bloom
四第合まって高まって
Waiting for the four elements, getting hyped
鎌を放て黒魔術
Release the scythe, black magic
せーの！此処に集えよ
One, two! Gather here
闇に震えけるメロス
Meros trembling in the darkness
切に響く言葉は
The words that echo earnestly
ぶち切れ発狂パラダイス
Are a snapping, maddening paradise
キラリ心落とすまで届け
Reach until you lose your sparkling heart
これからも私の元で
By my side from now on as well
不思議な力打ち放て
Unleash your mysterious power
世界は笑顔になっちゃって
The world will break out into smiles
ウラパパパパラリラ歌えば
If we sing Ura-pa-pa-pa-pa-ra-ri-ra
暗い顔などしてないで
生身の体さらだ 踊れよ
Don't make a dark face
Expose your body and dance
視界外部へ逸らさないで
Don't avert your eyes from outside your field of vision
今はただ離れていかないで
Don't leave right now
よいよい待ってあっち向いて
Wait, wait, look over there
今はまだ心の準備を
My heart isn't ready just yet
着替えさえ切って固まって
Change your clothes, freeze
ウタパパパ動き出す黒魔術
Utapapapa, black magic starts to move
我に続け今宵の
Follow me tonight
闇を破れ召し上がれよ
Break the darkness, help yourself
うつるべきものその名は
The thing that should be seen, its name is
眠りのはしお パラダイス
The edge of sleep, Paradise
キラリ心奥底まで届け
Sparkle, reach to the bottom of your heart
白黒つけてあげるから
I'll make it clear for you
不思議な力振りかざして
Wielding a mysterious power
みんなで笑顔になっちゃって
Everyone, let's all smile
ウタパパパラディラ歌えば
Utapapa-paradirah, if you sing
一緒一緒だよね
We're together, right?
みんなー！来てくれてありがとー！
Everyone! Thank you for coming!
まだまだ盛り上がっていくよー！
We're still going to get more hyped up!
ペンライト振ってねー！
Wave your penlights!
キラリキラリと紫に染まって
Twinkling, twinkling, dyed in purple
これからもあなたの元で
From now on too, by your side
奇跡の呪文解き放って
Release a miracle spell
咲かせる笑顔の花を
Let the flowers of smiles bloom
キラリ心奥底まで届け
Sparkle, reach to the bottom of your heart
これからも変わらないままで
Remaining unchanged from now on
不思議な力ほら宿って
Look, a mysterious power resides
世界も笑顔になっちゃって
The world will smile too
ウタパパパラディラ歌えば
Utapapa-paradirah, if you sing
一緒一緒だよね
We're together, right?
絶対一緒だよね
We're definitely together, right?
よー！ぽんぽんぽん！
Yo! Pon-pon-pon!
ぽんぽんぽん！
Pon-pon-pon!
百鬼夜行 音頭は上々
The Hyakki Yagyō march is excellent
今夜は眠れない
No sleeping tonight
レンジでやー！遊び尽くそう
Range de ya! Let's play to our hearts' content
万事一だったったった
Everything was perfect
天下無双溢れてくる
Peerless and overflowing
くすぐる好奇心
Tickling my curiosity
融通無碍これで決めよう
Flexible and free, let's decide with this
ジャンケンポンよさあ行こう
Rock-paper-scissors, let's go
パッとパッと開いた
Bursting open
あっとあっと言わせる
Let's make them gasp
花火を打ち上げよう
Let's set off some fireworks
歌え踊れ右に回れ
Sing, dance, turn to the right
意気揚々宵の宴
A high-spirited night banquet
さあ騒げよ集え
Now make some noise, gather
かれんなおにはうち
Lovely ogre in
歌え踊れ舞いなれもう
Sing, dance, dance some more
豪放磊落それすらも愛嬌
Bold and free, even that's charming
さあ騒げ明かすまで
Now make some noise until dawn
かれんなおにはうち
Lovely ogre in
天真爛漫言動大喝采
Innocent and cheerful words and actions, grand applause
お空に乗せられて
Carried by the sky
混ぜてて絶対派手に舞って
Mix it up, definitely dance flashily
天真爛漫よいのよいよい
Innocent and cheerful, evening good-good
ぽんぽんぽん！
Pon-pon-pon!
明鏡止水目を瞑って
Clear and serene, close your eyes
一息入れちゃって
Take a little breather
美味神味味わい尽くせ
Taste the divine flavor to the full
軽い日々だったったった
The days were light
永永無窮終わりたくない
Forever and ever, I don't want it to end
何して遊ぼうか
What shall we play?
安住忘却これで決めよう
Forgotten peace, let's decide with this
ジャンケンポンよさあ行こう
Rock-paper-scissors, let's go
グッとグッと堪えて
Bear it, bear it
ワッとワッと驚倒
Shocking them with a "wa!"
太鼓を打ち鳴らそう
Let's beat the drums
泣いて笑えよみ綴れ
Cry and laugh, write it all down
キラキラの響き掲げ
Hold up the sparkling resonance
さあおいで拒まず
Now come on, don't refuse
かれんなおにはうち
Lovely ogre in
泣いて笑え前進む期待値
Cry and laugh, the expected value of moving forward
下げでもいいぞ
It's okay even if it's lowered
さあおいで遠慮無用
Now come on, no need for restraint
かれんなおにはうち
Lovely ogre in
覆すほど夜を飾る
Decorating the night enough to overturn it
眩しい声に移ろられて
Moved by the dazzling voice
ならなら最高派手に舞って
Well then, dance most flashily
天真爛漫よいのよいよい
Innocent and cheerful, evening good-good
やっだぞー！今日はサードフェス！
We did it! Today is 3rd fes!
もっともっと盛り上げるために、みんなに「よいのて」してもらうよー！
To get even more hyped up, I'm going to have everyone do the "Yoino-te"!
余についてきてねー！
Follow me!
行くぞー！せーの！
Here we go! One, two!
よいよいよいよい！
Yoi yoi yoi yoi!
よいよいよいよいよい...
Yoi yoi yoi yoi yoi...
オッケー！
Okay!
せーせーのよいよいよい
Se-se-no-yoi-yoi-yoi
振り乱す
Shake it all about
せーせーのよいよいよい
Se-se-no-yoi-yoi-yoi
天を埋め尽くせ
Fill up the entire sky
唄え 踊れ 右輪で
Sing and dance by the water's edge
いきよいよい 愉快 千代の宴
With great vigor, a joyful eternal feast
さぁさぁ騒げ よろず前
Now, now, make some noise before everything
可憐な鬼は内へ
The lovely oni comes inside
唄え 踊れ 舞え 倣え
Sing, dance, perform, and follow along
ほう 骨の髄まで愛嬌
Oh, charming to the very marrow
さぁさぁ騒げ 暁まで
Now, now, make some noise until dawn
可憐な鬼は内へ
The lovely oni comes inside
理屈も無い事態 難題も手負う
In this illogical situation, facing even great challenges
音に乗せられて
Carried away by the sound
何てったって今派手に舞え
Because after all, perform flamboyantly now
千真爛漫 よいのよいのよい
Pure and bright, yoi no yoi no yoi
大神ミオ / OOKAMI MIO
Ookami Mio
兎田ぺこら / USADA PEKORA
Usada Pekora
角巻わため / TSUNOMAKI WATAME
Tsunomaki Watame
獅白ぼたん / SHISHIRO BOTAN
Shishiro Botan
明日の天気だとか
Whether it's tomorrow's weather
流行りのものも全部
Or even all the latest trends
あなたが今知りたいこと
Everything you want to know right now
あたしが皆教えるから
I'll tell you all about it
でもあなたが何を知りたいのか
But as for what it is you want to know
あたしは分からないんだよ
I really don't have a clue
三命学でも占星術でも
Whether by Sanmeigaku or astrology
タロット占いでもあたしたちの相性
Or even by tarot, our compatibility
最悪だけど
Is the absolute worst
動物占いならあたしたちは
But according to animal fortune-telling
相性抜群のカップルだって
We're a perfectly compatible couple
ねぇ こっち向いてよ
Hey, look this way
占いによりますと
According to the fortune-telling
あなたの悩み事は
As for your worries
あたしに全て話すことで
By telling me everything
身体ごと消えるのです
They'll disappear along with your body
でもあなたが何に悩んでいるのか
But as for what it is you're worrying about
あたしは分からないんだよ
I really don't have a clue
あたしはコアラで策略家だけど
I'm a Koala and a tactician
あなたの知らないところ多すぎて
But there's too much I don't know about you
ちょっと困ってるんだよ
I'm a little troubled by it
あなたは黒豹黙っていたって
You're a Black Panther, even if you stay quiet
いいところなら何だって知ってるよ
I know everything about your good points
ねぇ 伝えさせてよ
Hey, let me tell you
あたし本当は知っていたんだよ
I actually knew all along.
あなたがあの子を好きなの
That you like that girl.
動物占いなんて本当は
Animal horoscopes, actually,
これっぽっちだって興味ないんだ
I don't have the slightest interest in them.
なんか願掛けしたくて
I just wanted to make a wish for something.
あなたの視線を奪い続けてるあの子がいつもロマンチックだったのが
That girl who keeps stealing your gaze was always so romantic,
ちょっと悔しかったんだ
And it made me feel a bit frustrated.
数式でも占星術でも
Whether it's math or astrology,
タロット占いでも
Or even tarot cards,
あたしたちの相性
Our compatibility
最悪だけど
Is the absolute worst.
動物占い頼らなくたって
Even without relying on animal horoscopes,
あたしがあなたの好みに変わるから
I'll change to fit your tastes.
ねえ、こっち向いてよ
Hey, look this way.
DAY2無料パートは終了いたしました
The DAY 2 Free Portion has Ended
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!
DAY2無料パートは終了いたしました
The DAY2 free part has ended.
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!
hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish
DAY2無料パートは終了いたしました
The Day 2 free part has ended.
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!